

- SKILLS

React / Redux TypeScript JavaScript					
Material UI		HTML	CSS - Sass		Bootstrap
ООР	Git	GraphC	QL N	ode js	Express
Postgres		MongoDl	3		

MUZAFFARBEK **ABDUSAMATOV**

Front-end Developer

- ABOUT ME

Hello. My name is Muzaffarbek.

I am experienced web developer. My role is to write and style the frontend components that meet the requirements of our mocks and fulfil our user stories.

Almost I use professionally with React, TypeScript, JavaScript, OOP, GraphQL, CSS SASS, Node js, Express js, EJS... In addition, I can easily work in a team

Speak languages

Uzbek	
English	
Russian	

- CONTACT

- **(**) +998 99 458 33 68
- genrofer@gmail.com
- www.genrofer.cf
- in linkedin.com/in/amuzaffarbe

Udemy

- EDUCATION HISTORY

Online Courses Jan 2018 - July 2019

Najot Ta'lim

Education Centre in Tashkent Aug 2021 - May 2022

- WORK EXPERIENCE

Front end Developer

XXI asr buxgaltery Mar 2019 - Sep 2019

English teacher

English teacher Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

Full Stack Developer

Yosh Tadbirkor University Aug 2021 - May 2022